<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

     <string name="fire_tools_title">Digital Pointer Tools</string>
     <string name="SPI_prompt">Press the DP button to toggle between movable and pinned state. Long press to remove.</string>
     <string name="enable_grg_interact">Enable Image Overlay Map Interaction</string>
     <string name="enable_grg_interact_summ">Enable to allow interaction with Image Overlays on the map when the outline is visible.   If no outline is visible, then the Image Overlay cannot be interacted with.  If this is false, no interaction can occur even if the outline is visible.</string>
     <string name="delete_grg">Delete Image Overlay</string>
     <string name="grg">Image Overlay\u0020</string>
     <string name="grg_file">Image Overlay File</string>
     <string name="grg_lowercase">image overlay</string>
     <string name="grgLayerPreferences">Image Overlay Outline Preferences</string>
     <string name="fire_control_prefs">Digital Pointer Toolbar Preferences</string>
     <string name="fires_prefs">Digital Pointer Preferences</string>
     <string name="adjust_fire_settings">Adjust preferences for the Digital Pointer toolbar</string>
     <string name="cot2525B" translatable="false">Markers</string>
     <string name="s2525B">Markers</string>
     <string name="default_cot_mapping">Default Mapping</string>
     <string name="tadilj_settings">Datalink Preferences</string>
     <string name="tadilj_id">My Datalink Id</string>
     <string name="tadilj_id2">Datalink ID</string>
     <string name="tadilj_self_type">Which type of Datalink message to send for self-SA messages</string>
     <string name="tadilj_track_block">This is the start of the block of Datalink IDs that should be auto-assigned to hostiles</string>
     <string name="tadilj_settings_summary">Manage settings for Datalink messages</string>
     <string name="managePersistedIdsSummary">Tap to manage Persisted Datalink IDs</string>
     <string name="showTadiljIdsTitle">Show Datalink IDs</string>
     <string name="showTadiljIdsSummary">If checked other users\' Datalink IDs will appear on the map</string>
     <string name="replaceTadiljIdsCallsignTitle">Replace s with Datalink ID</string>
     <string name="replaceTadiljIdsCallsignSummary">In the Self Coordinate Display, replace the callsign with the Datalink ID</string>
     <string name="preferences_text438">Reset Datalink offset</string>
     <string name="details_text50">"Enter Datalink info: "</string>
     <string name="details_text52">"Clear all Datalink contacts? "</string>
     <string name="stringSPIDesc">Toggle the DP tool.</string>
     <string name="quick_select_spi">Quick Select DP</string>
     <string name="tool_text31">The Digital Pointer (DP) has a menu item that when selected allows the DP to be dragged around the radius to correct issues introduced by the magnetic compass in the Laser Range Finder.   The red cone displays a 10 degree offset of either side of the reported shot to aid in correction.</string>
     <string name="place_local_spi">Place Local DP</string>
     <string name="spi_update_delay">DP Update Period</string>
     <string name="spi_update_delay_summary">The maximum delay between sending updates for the DP point, if enabled (in seconds) even if the DP is not modified.   Moving a DP point locally will generate updates immediately.</string>
     <string translatable="false" name="spi_abbrev">DP</string>
     <string name="bloodhound_text9">Enable Auto Zoom feature to display self and DP in map view when tool is first launched</string>
     <string name="imagery_change_summ">In this version, the Image Overlay tab has been fully migrated to the Overlay Manager.\nImage Overlay files, in TIF or KMZ file format, should be placed in the atak/grg folder on either the sdcard or the internal memory.\n\nImagery based map products (pfps, native, layers) should now be placed in the atak/imagery folder either on the sdcard or the internal memory.\n\nOverlay products like KML, KMZ, LPT, DRW, etc should be placed in the atak/overlay folder either on the sdcard or internal memory.</string>
     <string name="point_dropper_text40">Invalid DP update delay set. Resetting to default value 5.</string>
     <string translatable="false" name="repeater_in_contact">In Contact</string>
     <string name="fireSpiNumber">Number of DP</string>
     <string name="fireSpiNumberSummary">Number of DPs to show in the Digital Pointer toolbar</string>
     <string name="spi_redx_fah">DP/RedX FAH Width</string>
     <string name="spi_redx_fah_summary">Sets the width of the FAH cone (in degrees) when enabled from a DP or the Red X (rounds to the closest increment of 10)</string>
     <string name="actionbar_firetools">Digital Pointer Tools</string>
</resources>
